Guide to the Thomas M. Disch Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- June 1991 Acquisition, 1956-1991; 23.04; (25 boxes)
  - Writings, Series I
    - "Theory of Fiction," essay, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "Thirteen Great Works of Fantasy From the Last 16 Years," and "Thirteen Classics of Fantasy," lists, typescript, undated
    - "This Little Pig Had None," short story, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "Thoughts Ed's Movie Made Me Think," free writing, typescript, undated
    - "Three Excerpts from the Complete Rhyming Dictionary and Poet's Craft Book by Clement Wood," poems, 2 copies, undated
    - "Three Temple Songs," poems, typescript, 2 copies, undated
    - "$3.20," short story, typescript, undated
    - "To An Unknown Copy Editor," poem, typescript, with manuscript notes, undated
    - "To be enclosed by green and living things...," poem, typescript, undated
    - "To the Evening Star," poem, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "To the Fates," poem by Friedrich Holderlin, typescript, undated
    - "To Jean-Ann," poem, typescript, 2 copies, undated
    - "To Jim," poem, typescript, undated
    - "To Stop Without a Reason," poem, typescript, undated
    - "To a Young Mother Who Paints," poem, typescript, undated
    - "Tom Swift," press release: printed materials, with autograph notes, 1990
    - "Toot! Toot! Toot!," poem, typescript, undated
    - "Torturing Mr. Amberwell," novella, typescript and galleys, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "Troll Notebook #1," notebook, autograph manuscript, undated
    - "Troll Notebook #2," notebook, autograph manuscript, undated
    - The Troll of Surewould Forest, novel, typescript, with autograph notes and corrections, and published clippings, undated; 5
    - "The Turtle's Dream," poem, typescript, 3 copies, undated
    - Twelve Portraits, poetry collection, typescript, undated; 2
    - Twilight Zone Magazine payment receipts, 1982-1984
    - "Two Poems in One Night," poem, typescript, 2 copies, undated
    - "Under Compulsion," financial records, 1970
    - "Understanding Human Behavior," short story, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "United We Stand Still," short story, typescript, undated
    - "The Universe Considered As Modern Dance," short story, typescript, undated
    - Untitled poems, 14 poems and accompanying letter, typescript, undated
    - "Upon Being Forbidden Entrance to a Castle," poem, typescript, 2 copies, 1966 July
    - "The Uses of Darkness," poem, typescript, 3 copies, undated
    - "The Uses of Fiction," essay, typescript, undated
    - "'Utopia? Never! The Visitor Said," short story, typescript, undated
    - "A Vacation on Earth," poem, typescript, 3 copies, undated
    - "A Valediction," poem, published clipping, 1975 August
    - "The Vamp," short story, typescript, undated
    - "Vertigo," poem, typescript, 3 copies, undated
    - "Very Like a Whale," short story, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "Vespers," poem, typescript, undated
    - "The Vindication of Obesity," poem, typescript, with autograph notes and corrections, undated
    - "Voices of the Kill" (short story)
      - Typescript, with manuscript notes, undated
      - Typescript, with autograph corrections, 2 copies, undated
      - Typescript, photocopy, undated
    - "Waking Early on New Year's 1983, Without a Hangover," poem, typescript, with autograph corrections, 1983 January 1
    - "Waking in a Strange Apartment," poem, typescript, 2 copies, undated
    - "The Wandering Jew," short story, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "The Way to a Man's Heart," short story, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "We Are Divided Everywhere in Two Parts," poem, draft and typescript, accompanied by note, 1989 March 23
    - "The West Coast," poem, typescript, 2 copies, undated
    - "what can i say," poem, typescript, undated
    - "What Can the Matter Be?," poem, typescript, undated
    - "What Can You Say About Pork and Beans?," short story, typescript, 2 copies, 1964-1965
    - "What the Group Thought," poem, typescript, undated
    - "What to Accept," poem, typescript, undated
    - "When I think of you," poem, typescript, 1967 January 28
    - "Whether That Was Love," poem, typescript, undated
    - "The Who, What, and How of Grokking SF," essay, typescript, undated
    - "Wholeness, Harmony, Radiance," poem, typescript, undated
    - "Why I Paint," essay, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "Why I Write Poetry," poem, typescript, undated
    - "The William Tell Overture," poem, typescript, undated
    - "The Women of Bogazkoy," and other first drafts of poems, typescript, with manuscript notes, 1990
    - "The Wonderful World of Griswald Tractors," short story, typescript and published clipping, undated
    - "Work," short story, typescript, with autograph notes and corrections, undated
    - "Working on a Tan," poem, typescript, with autograph corrections, 2 copies, undated
    - "Writing More Poems," poem, typescript, undated
    - "Xmas," short story, typescript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - "Yesterday," poem, typescript, undated
    - "You Are On the Communists' List," short story, typescript, undated
    - "The Young Love," poem, typescript, dated on his 27th birthday, undated
    - Unidentified fragments, typescript and manuscript, with autograph corrections, undated
    - Unidentified typescripts, with autograph corrections, undated; 2
  - Correspondence, Series II
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - "A" general, 1967-1982, undated (Box 14)
    - Advertising agencies, 1963-1964; 3
    - Aldiss, Brian, 1974-1976
    - Andersson, Kent, 1961-1983
    - Andrevon, J. P., 1970-1971, undated
    - Arnason, Eleanor, 1973
    - "B" general, 1959-1985, undated; 7
    - The Bellevue Press, 1975-1985
    - Berkeley Publishing Corp., 1970-1979
    - Blazer, Samuel, 1969-1981; 3
    - Braly, Malcolm, 1968-1974, undated; 2
    - Brandt & Brandt, 1967-1974; 3
    - Briggs, John, 1965-1971, undated; 3
    - "C" general, 1964-1988, undated; 4
    - Carr, Terry, 1966-1967
    - Clarion correspondence, 1974-1975
    - Clute, John and Judith, 1963-1985, undated; 7
    - Collin, Frances, 1971-1978, undated; 8
    - "D" general, 1963-1987, undated; 4
    - Dann, Jack, 1975
    - Davidson, Avram and Grania, 1964-1965, 1975; 2
    - Delany, Samuel R., 1967-1980; 6
    - Dick, Philip K., 1972-1975; 2
    - Dick, Philip K. Award, 1982-1984; 2
    - Dickson, Gordon E., 1970 July 21
    - Disch, Aurelia, 1970-1972
    - Disch, Felix and Mrs., 1958-1968; 5
    - Disch, Felix, 1969-1979, undated; 7 (Box 15)
    - Disch, Gary, 1959-1980, undated; 4
    - Disch, "Grandma", 1967 January
    - Disch, Greg and Linda, 1965-1984; 3
    - Disch, Jeff and family, 1963-1986; 7
    - Disch, Nancy, 1960-1985; 4
    - Dizenzo, Patricia and Charles, 1965-1981, undated; 3
    - Doubleday and Company, 1966-1970
    - "E" general, 1975-1985, undated
    - Edwards, Malcolm, 1971 June
    - Effinger, G. A. "Piglet", [1969]-1970
    - Ellison, Harlan, 1971-1979
    - "F" general, 1963-1982; 2
    - Farmer, Phillip Jose, 1969-1975
    - Farrar, Straus, & Giroux, 1973
    - Freer, Janet, 1967-1975, undated; 5
    - "G" general, 1968-1985, undated; 2
    - Gillespie, Bruce, 1973-1981; 2
    - Ginzberg, Gerry, 1975-1976
    - Gregg, Stephen, 1971
    - "H" general, 1967-1984, undated
    - Hacker, Marilyn, 1968-1984, undated; 2
    - Hall, Melissa Mia, 1981-1984
    - Harper & Row, Publishers, 1972-1980, undated
    - Harrison, Harry, 1970-1975
    - Harrison, M. John, 1974-1978
    - Hart-Davis, MacGibbon Ltd., 1973-1974
    - Harwood, Lee, 1970-1973
    - Hemp, Christine (toaster artist), 1986 May 5
    - Hensgens, Kay and Gil, 1959-1962, undated
    - Hutchinson Publishing Group, 1972-1980
    - "I" general, 1962-1980, undated
    - Iverson, Alan, 1959-1966, undated
    - "J" general, 1968-1982, undated
    - "K" general, 1963-1983, undated
    - Kearns, Winifred, 1975
    - Kidd, Virginia, 1969-1985, undated; 5
    - Kielty, James, 1973-1974
    - Knight, Damon and Kate Wilhelm, 1965-1971
    - "L" general, 1956-1985, undated
    - Leguin, Ursula K., 1973, 1974
    - Lehman, David, 1982-1984; 2
    - Leiber, Fritz, 1975 April 3 (Box 16)
    - Lunde, David and Mary Lee, 1968-1972, undated
    - Lunde, Diane, 1972-1977, undated; 3
    - Lupoff, Richard, 1976-1985
    - "M" general, 1965-1986, undated; 3
    - McAllister, Bruce, 1975-1981
    - McIntyre, Vonda, 1972 October 7
    - Marchetti, Doris, 1977-1981
    - The Massachusetts Review, 1970-1971
    - Merrill, Judith, 1965-1972
    - Mills, Robert P., 1965-1969; 2
    - Moorcock, Michael and Hilary, 1966-1984; 4
    - Mundis, Hester and Jerry, 1964-1978, undated; 7
    - Myers, Gale and Dan, 1974-1976
    - "N" general, 1962-1984, undated
    - Naylor, Charles, 1969-1980; 2
    - "O" general, 1975-1984
    - "P" general, 1966-1983
    - Padgett, Ron, 1967-1971
    - Paulsen, Kathryn, 1973-1981
    - Platt, Charles, 1969-1982; 2
    - Priest, Christopher, 1974-1980
    - "Q" general, 1966-1978
    - "R" general, 1965-1984, undated; 2
    - Reed, Kit, 1971-1976
    - Rottger, Betty, 1987 May 19
    - Rubinstein, Hilary, 1973-1979; 3
    - Rush, Norman, 1970-1981; 3
    - Russ, Joanna, 1968-1973; 2
    - "S" general, 1957-1984, undated; 8
    - Sallis, James and Jane, 1966-1984, undated; 4
    - Sarch, Kenneth, 1960-1969; 2
    - Saunders, Kraig, 1963-1973; 2
    - Schjeldahl, Peter, 1967-1972 (Box 17)
    - Scott Meredith Literary Agency, 1964-1981, undated; 5
    - Scott, Philippa, 1967-1970
    - Shaw, Richard and Sarah, 1957-1973
    - Sheckley, Robert, 1974-1979
    - Silverberg, Robert, 1971-1973
    - Sladek, John and Pamela, 1964-1984, undated; 12
    - Suvin, Darko, 1970-1974
    - "T" general, 1968-1987; 2
    - "U" general, 1970-1980
    - "V" general, 1960-1984
    - "W" general, 1971-1984; 4
    - Wickstrom, Lois, 1979-1981; 2
    - Wolfe, Gene, 1970-1972
    - "X" general, undated
    - "Y" general, 1981
    - Zelazny, Roger, 1972-1974
    - Zoline, Pamela, 1963-1981; 3
    - "Bill", 1972-73
    - "Jan", 1960
    - "Jim", 1960
    - "Judy", 1960, undated
    - Various "Pamelas", 1963, 1966, undated
    - Unidentified, 1961-1985, undated; 9
  - Other Papers, Series III
    Organized into four subseries: Financial Papers, Stage Production Programs, Writings of Others, Other Papers.
    - Financial Papers
      - Apartment records, 1969-1976; 7 (Box 18)
      - Art Students' League receipts, 1979-1980; 2
      - Banking records, 1972-1978; 5
      - Bills and receipts, 1963-1983; 32
      - Checking records, 1964-1976; 6
      - Checking records, 1976-1978; 7 (Box 19)
      - Cash management account, 1982-1985; 2
      - College transcript, 1970
      - Deposit slips, 1973-1976
      - House sale contract, 1975
      - Loan forms, 1961
      - Loan applications, 1975; 2
      - Retirement accounts, 1982-1983; 2
      - Tax records, 1961-1978; 11
      - Miscellany, 1981, undated
    - Stage Production Programs
      Arranged alphabetically by title.
      - A, 1987-1991; 4
      - B, 1986-1989; 2
      - B, 1987-1991; 3 (Box 20)
      - C, 1986-1990; 6
      - D-E, 1987-1990; 3
      - F-G, 1989-1991; 5
      - H-I, 1987-1990; 2
      - H-I, 1987-1991, undated; 2 (Box 21)
      - J-L, 1985-1991; 5
      - M, 1983-1990; 5
      - N-O, 1987-1991; 3
      - P, 1985-1991; 4
      - R, 1986-1991; 3 (Box 22)
      - S, 1985-1991; 5
      - T, 1987-1991; 4
      - U-V, 1987-1991; 2
      - W, 1987-1990; 5
      - Y-Z, 1988-1989, undated; 2
    - Writings of Others
      Arranged alphabetically by author.
      - Baker, Russell. The Good Times, novel, bound galleys, uncorrected, 1989 (Box 23)
      - Benford, Gregory. "Centigrade 233," short story, typescript, with accompanying correspondence, 1989
      - Burton, Jeffrey. "The Misbourne Identity," short story, typescript, photocopy, with cover letter, 1987
      - Carr, Terry. "Buddha with a Light Bulb," short story, photocopy of clipping, undated
      - Crabtree, Lee. "Memoir," photocopied booklet, circa 1973
      - Crichton, Michael. Sphere, novel, bound proof, uncorrected, 1987
      - Dick, Philip K. The Man Whose Teeth Were All Exactly Alike, advertisement, 1984
      - Hacker, Marilyn. The Terrible Children, poetry collection, photocopy, 1967
      - Hochberg, Norman. "The Number You Have Reached," screenplay, typescript, carbon, with accompanying correspondence, 1972
      - Hofstra, Jan. 'Chloeen, in prinsesse,' poetry, in Quatrebras, a periodical in Dutch, 1960
      - Jones, Jack. "To the End of Thought," essay, typescript, undated
      - Kletter, Richard. "Flying: screenplay for On Wings of Song," typescript, photocopy, 1981
      - McWilliam, Candia. A Little Stranger, novel, review copy, 1989
      - Moorcock, Michael and Philip James. The Distant Suns, comic book, 1975
      - Mulisch, Harry. Last Call, novel, proofs, bound, uncorrected, 1989
      - Mundis, Jerrold. "Even Primitive Man," short story, typescript, undated
      - Payne, John. Avon Reader's Report on "No Room for Suspicion," typescript, 1970
      - Sallis, James. Poems, typescript, undated
      - Schjeldahl, Peter
        - "From a Honeymoon Journal," short story, typescript, photocopy, with cover letter, 1975
        - Dreams, prose poetry collection, published copy, 1974
      - Sladek, John. "Red Noise," short story, typescript, photocopy, with manuscript notes, 1982, undated
      - Starkweather, David. "Three Poems," typescript, undated
      - Zoline, Pamela. Sheep, novel, typescript, photocopy, undated
      - Unidentified. Poetry Project: newsletter with poems, typescript and photocopy, 1979
    - Other Papers
      - Black & Decker drill instructions, undated
      - British Institute of Florence: flyer, 1972
      - Clute, Judith, exhibition pamphlet, 1974
      - Daily Reminder: empty planner book, 1960
      - "Dead Mother," 2 reviews of a play by D. Greenspan, clippings, 1991
      - Drawings: artists unknown, 1972-1987
      - Forty-Eighth International PEN Congress: program of events, 1986
      - Ice Capades, program of events, 1987
      - Life insurance course, certificate of completion, 1960
      - Maps, 1970-1975; 3
      - Medical record, 1975
      - Passport, 1964
      - Pozzo's Perspectives, four printed pages, receipt from B. Weinreb LTD, 1972, undated
      - Small press flyers, 1982
      - Tourist pamphlets, undated
      - Travel Companion [Espanola], 1965
      - Telluride clippings, 1987
- October 1994 Acquisition, 1967-1993; 5.42; (6 boxes)
  Organized into two series: I. Writings. II. Other Papers.
  - Writings, Series I
    Chiefly arranged alphabetically by title.
    - "Apollo," typescript, undated (Box 26)
    - Angouleme, partial draft, undated
    - "Black Alive," by Thom Demijohn, galley, 1968
    - "The Black Cat," typescript, undated
    - The Brave Little Toaster, fragments, undated
    - The Businessman, drafts, 1992; 6
    - "Clara Reeve, Book I," typescript, photocopy, undated
    - The Colors, photocopy, undated
    - "Dark Verses and Light," typescript and galley, circa 1991; 2
    - "The Death of Socrates," galley, undated
    - "The Foetus," typescript, undated
    - "The Fountains of Paradise," typescript, undated
    - "The Furth....," Atlantic Monthly article, proof, photocopy, 1991
    - "A Kiss Goodbye," typescript, undated
    - "Knowing What You Like: A Philistine's Guide to the National Gallery," typescript, undated
    - "The Joycelin Shrager Story," typescript, undated
    - "Live From Gologotha: The Gospel According to Gore Vidal," proof, 1992
    - The M.D.: A Horror Story (novel)
      - Drafts and proofs, circa 1991; 2
      - Drafts and proofs, circa 1991; 4 (Box 27)
      - Book cover, book jackets, 1991
    - "Misremembering John Crowley," typescript, undated
    - "Mythology and Science Fiction: Introduction," typescript, undated
    - "The New Look for Men," typescript, undated
    - "On the Wings of Song," various drafts, undated; 7
    - "The Priest. A Gothic Romance," proposal for a novel, typescript, undated (Box 28)
    - "The Penis and the Sword: Uncoding the Debate About Gays in the Military," typescript, undated
    - The Prisoner, a novel based on the television series, outline, first draft, notes, and map, undated; 2
    - "Quincunx," typescript, undated
    - "The Ruins of the Earth," uncorrected proof copy, 1972
    - 334, various drafts, undated; 7
    - A Troll of Surewould Forest, drafts, 1992; 3
    - Theater reviews, typescript and printed, 1993, undated
    - "The Vengeance of Hera," typescript, undated (Box 29)
    - "The Women of Bogazkoy, or The Invasion of the Hittite Hordes. A Satyr Play," typescript, undated
    - "A World of Ill Manners," typescript, undated
    - Yes, Let's: New and Selected Poems, proof, with related correspondence, 1989
    - Untitled article, typescript, undated
    - Fragments, poetry and prose, undated; 2
    - Hastings, Victor: "Alfred the Great," typescript, undated
  - Other Papers, Series II
    - Clippings about Flags, 1989 (Box 30)
    - Correspondence, contracts. France and other publishers, 1978-1983
    - Larry McCaffery interview, typescript, 1988
    - Medea Project, typescripts, correspondence, 1977; 3
    - Royalty statements, United States and United Kingdom, 1975-1985; 4
    - The Scholastic Art and Writing Awards, typescripts and correspondence, 1993
    - United States Information Service and United States Information Agency, correspondence, typescripts, notes, and printed material, portions in Spanish, relating to Thomas Disch and South America, 1990-1991; 9
    - Newspapers, 1990-1991
    - Printed material, 1991; 3
    - Office files of Fran Collin (Agent of Thomas Disch), 1967-1982; 16 (Box 31)
- January 2000 Acquisition, 1964-1998; 11.71; (15 boxes)
  Organized into four series: I. Writings. II. Correspondence. III. Electronic Files. IV. Audiovisual Material.
  - Writings, Series I
    Not arranged in any particular order.
    - The Dreams Our Stuff Is Made Of, typescript, 1998; 6 (Box 32)
    - "A Child's Garden of Grammar"
      - Original cover art and typeset, typescript copies with reviews, 1997; 2
      - Copy-edited manuscript, original art work and editorial correspondence, 1997; 2
    - "Minnesota Gothic," edited typescript, undated
    - "The Affluence of Edwin Lollard," edited typescript, undated
    - "The Vamp," edited typescript with editorial correspondence, undated
    - "Three Points on the Demographic Curve," edited typescript, undated
    - "Souvenirs," (Early draft of A Kiss Goodbye), edited typescript, undated
    - "The Homeostats," (Early draft of Nada) edited typescript, undated
    - "The Future of the Book: A Prophecy," edited typescript with copies, undated
    - The M.D.
      - Edited typescript, 1991; 6
      - Typescript, pages 1-102 only, 1991
      - Contract and correspondence from the Russian publishing agent, 1993
    - "Neighbors," heavily edited version with layout corrections and editorial correspondence, 1981; 7
    - The Priest
      - Author's 1st pass, 1994; 3 (Box 33)
      - Author's 2nd pass, 1994; 3
      - Master set 1st pass, 1994; 3
      - Master set 2nd pass, 1994; 3
      - Heavily edited typescript with layout corrections, 1994; 5
      - Reviews and editorial correspondence, 1994
      - Edited typescript, 1994; 5
      - Edited typescript, 1994; 5 (Box 34)
      - 2 paperback typescript layouts, 1994; 3
      - Edited typescript, 1994; 5
      - Random typeset pages, 1994
      - Proposal for novel, holograph notes, editorial and general correspondence, related newspaper clippings, original cover, and numerous issues of The Lambda Update, 1993-1994
    - The Sub: A Study in Witchcraft
      - Proposal for the novel and books log, 1999
      - Author's 1st pass, 1999; 3
      - Author's 2nd pass with editorial correspondence [3 folders], 1999; 3
      - Master 1st pass, 1999; 3 (Box 35)
      - Master proof 2nd pass, 1999; 3
      - Photocopy of edited typescript, 1999; 5
      - Pages from typescript, 1999
      - Edited typescript copy, 1999; 5
      - Typescript sheets, 1999
      - Correspondence and prison material, 1998
    - Miami Vice, "Missing Hours," revised script, premise for the episode, edited typescript version of plot, contracts and residual statement, notes, TV Guide and newspaper review, correspondence, future story lines and Emmy Awards entrant proof, 1978-1988
    - "Ben Hur: A Play in Four Acts," edited typescript copies and some related correspondence, 1996
    - "Chanson Perpetuelle," photocopy of paperback version, undated
    - The Black Lotus (screenplay)
      - Outline, typescript and correspondence, 1985; 2
      - Screenplay, 1991
      - Treatment and outline, typescipt, 1991 (Box 36)
    - "Amnesia," typescript copy of screenplay with some related correspondence, 1985; 2
    - An assortment of essays, short stories, poetry and correspondence, [1970-1999]; 21
    - Theater, book and movie reviews, [1970-1999]; 13 (Box 37)
    - "The Brave Little Toaster Goes to Mars," stage adaptation by Dan Hurlin, production script, 1990
    - "Understanding Human Behavior," screenplay first draft, 1986
    - "Camp Concentration," stage adaptation and correspondence, 1987
    - "The Number You Have Reached," screenplay adaptation final draft, 1997
    - "Wings," first draft, based on the novel On Wings of Song by Thomas Disch, 1981
    - "Frankenstein," libretto by Thomas Disch for the opera by Gregory Sandow, 1981
    - "Particulars," poem by Thomas Disch, music by Sarch, original sheet music, 1963
    - The Hudson Review, correspondence and typescripts, 1997
    - Essays, and short stories from Harpers, Swank and Crawdaddy, 1974-1976
    - Address books, [1975]; 3
    - Notebook: The M.D., draft and National Review, undated
    - Notebook: The M.D., undated
    - Notebook: poems, undated
    - Composition book: notes and writings, undated
    - Contracts, royalty statements and correspondence with various publishing companies, 1979-1985
    - Manuscript poems, notes, and ideas, undated
    - Correspondence and other papers relating to high school reunions, 1977-1982
    - "Nosepickers," a series of drawings, undated
    - Jacket covers and art work from various books, undated
    - "Computer information" (user guides), 1983-1985
    - "The Roswell Incident," words and music by Suzanne McDermott, 1998
      Scope and Contents
      Includes letter to Disch from Suzanne McDermott
    - National Book Critics Circle: correspondence, business meetings, publications and notes, 1989-1995; 5 (Box 38)
    - World Trips: information and schedules relating to Science Fiction Seminars, 1989; 2
    - Interview with Thomas Disch, edited typescript, undated
    - "Wild Palms," a copy of the script with some related correspondence., 1992
    - Magazines, journals and newspaper clippings, [1960-1995]; 4
    - Stage production programs, 1980-1995; 5
    - Stage production programs, 1980-1995; 11 (Box 39)
    - The New York Press, 1998 October (Box 40 (Oversize))
    - Backstage, 1998 October 16
  - Correspondence, Series II
    - Scholarship application and related correspondence, 1970 (Box 41)
    - Medical coverage and doctors visits, 1987-1998
    - Rejection letters and other editorial correspondence, [1970-1998]; 7
    - Poetry letters, [1979-1993]; 3
    - Letters from Thomas Disch to Pat and Charlie [Dizenzoes], 1964-1965
    - Fan mail, 1968-1975; 3
    - Letters from Elizabeth Jolley, 1986-1990
    - General correspondence, 1964-1986; 10
    - General correspondence, 1987-1998, undated; 14 (Box 42)
  - Electronic Files, Series III